Guide to the Farm Bureau scrapbooks, New York State, 1912-1934
Farm Bureau scrapbooks, New York State, 1912-1934
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Farm Bureau scrapbooks, New York State, 1912-1934.
21-24-461
4.2 cubic ft.
Scrapbooks.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Scrapbooks documenting farm bureau activities county by county, 1912-1917; also two scrapbooks on farm bureau activity statewide, 1928-1934.
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
Between 1911 and 1918, Farm Bureaus were organized by Cornell's College of Agriculture in most rural counties in New York State, before 1914 with the assistance of Sears Roebuck, railroads, chambers of commerce, and other business groups, after 1914 with federal aid provided under the Smith-Lever Act. In 1918, these bureaus and those which had been organized simultaneously in other states organized nationally as the American Farm Bureau Federation. Within New York, the county farm bureaus were organized as the New York State Farm Bureau Federation. The integration of Cooeperative Extension and the Farm Bureaus continued in New York State into the 1950s, when separation was mandated by the federal government.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Scrapbooks documenting farm bureau activities county by county, 1912-1917; also two scrapbooks on farm bureau activity statewide, 1928-1934.
SUBJECTS
Names:
American Farm Bureau Federation.; New York State Farm Bureau Federation.
Subjects:
Agriculture--Societies, etc.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Albany, 1915-1917 (Box 1)
- Allegany, 1913-1918 (Box 1)
- Broome, 1914-1917 (Box 1)
- Cattaraugus, 1913-1918 (Box 2)
- Cayuga, 1914-1918 (Box 2)
- Chautauqua, 1913-1917 (Box 2)
- Chemung, 1912-1918 (Box 3)
- Chenango, 1915-1918 (Box 3)
- Clinton, 1912-1917 (Box 3)
- Columbia, 1917-1918 (Box 4)
- Cortland, 1913-1917 (Box 4)
- Delaware, 1914-1917 (Box 4)
- Dutchess, 1914-1918 (Box 4)
- Erie, 1913-1917 (Box 5)
- Franklin, 1913-1917 (Box 5)
- Genesee, 1917-1918 (Box 5)
- Jefferson, 1913-1918 (Box 5)
- Livingston, 1917 (Box 6)
- Madison, 1915-1917 (Box 6)
- Monroe, 1913-1916 (Box 6)
- Montgomery, 1914-1918 (Box 6)
- Nassau, 1914-1918 (Box 7)
- Niagara, 1913-1917 (Box 7)
- Oneida, 1914-1918 (Box 8)
- Onondaga, 1915-1917 (Box 8)
- Ontario, 1916-1917 (Box 8)
- Orange, 1915-1918 (Box 8)
- Orleans, 1917-1918 (Box 9)
- Oswego, 1914-1918 (Box 9)
- Otsego, 1914-1917 (Box 9)
- Rennselaer, 1916-1918 (Box 9)
- St. Lawrence, 1914-1917 (Box 10)
- Saratoga, 1914-1917 (Box 10)
- Schoharie, 1915-1918 (Box 10)
- Seneca, 1915-1918 (Box 10)
- Steuben, 1915-1918 (Box 10)
- Suffolk, 1917 (Box 10)
- Sullivan, 1915-1917 (Box 11)
- Tioga, 1914-1917 (Box 11)
- Tompkins, 1914-1918 (Box 11)
- Ulster, 1914-1918 (Box 12)
- Wayne, 1917-1918 (Box 12)
- Wyoming, 1913-1918 (Box 12)
- Yates, 1918 (Box 12)
- Alfalfa-Clover Campaign, 1924-1929 (Box 13)
- Empire State Potato Club, 1931 (Box 13)
- Woodchuck Control, 1926 (Box 14)
- New York State Farm Bureau, 1932-1934 (Box 14)